Mert Kaan İrtegün Frontend Developer

™ mertkaan255@gmail.com

+905332594935

Soganlik Altas Street Kartal/ Istanbul - Turkey

k https://mertkaanirtegun.netlify.app/

https://github.com/kaanirtegun8

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/mert-kaan-irteg%C3%BCn-0490541b5/



Profile

Front-end developer with proven experience in Armut(Homerun in Europe), Poplar and Insider, helping companies develop new features and improve existing code contents. Knows modern javascript frameworks and libraries, is open to learning and closely follows new developments in the software world.

Professional Experience

Armut | Homerun, Frontend Developer 2022 - present • Responsible for developing new features, improving existing code quality Istanbul, Turkey • Angular, SCSS, javascript, Jenkins, Vue, Jest, Cypress 07/2021 - 02/2022 Kavak, Frontend Developer Istanbul, Turkey · Responsible for the establishment and development of the architecture of newly created projects • Responsible for improving the SEO scores of the projects created • Vue 2, Nuxt, Vuex, Vuetify, HTML/Twig, Less, Javascript (Vanilla.js) **Insider,** Javascript Developer ☑ 01/2021 - 07/2021 Istanbul, Turkey • Responsible for the development of campaigns and adding new features, created in accordance with the agreements of Insider, Turkey's first unicorn company, with world-famous brands. • Javascript, Jquery, Vue, Vuex

Skills

Vue Nuxt, Vuex, Vue 2-3, Vuetify	• • • •	React Redux	• • • • •
Angular NgRx	• • • •	Javascript Typescript, Node.js, Jquery, Vanilla.js, ES6, ES7	••••
C/C++/Python	• • • •	Database MongoDB, MySQL, MsSQL, PostgreSQL	••••

Education

09/2016 – 02/2022 Istanbul, Turkey

Istanbul Technical University, Bachelor's degree ☑

• I have worked as a full stack developer in many software projects throughout my academic life at Turkey's best technical university, which has agreements with many universities in the world.

Languages

English		
Speaking: B2		
Reading/Writing: C1		
Listening: C1		

French Speaking: A1 Reading/Writing: A2 Listening: A2

German Speaking: A1 Reading/Writing: A2 Listening: A1